Thank you.
Which class are you in?
Twelfth.
And what do you want to be:
Engineer or Doctor?
- Haven't decided yet, uncle.
- No, thank you.
So, you have two children?
No. We have Lola too!
He really treats Lola
like our third child!
He's really fond of her.
Dogs are very loyal.
Richa, come in.
Hello.
Sit.
We have a daughter too.
Call her. Do a video call.
She's married to a doctor,
and she's expecting now.
The network is poor.
WiFi password?
A1B2C3D4E5F6
What?
A1, B-
2...
2,C...
3...
D?
4...
E?
5...
F6
Now that's an instant connection!
Did you have trouble
finding the house?
Not really.
Rang a couple of wrong bells,
but we found the house.
What kind of doctor are you?
Doctor of female anatomy.
Wow!
I've never met
a male gynac before.
It's a compliment, right?
Yes.
I've never been here,
but we eat out often.
I love pizza.
And my favorite, Cassata!
Why don't you taste this!
What do you like?
I like simple, home-cooked food.
Nothing quite like it.
In the soft hum of a morning anew
Whispers of hope, like gentle dew
Let's journey together
Forever
In this joyous radiant light
All our desires burn bright
Let's journey together
Forever
Welcome to the family!
You're our daughter now.
Slowly awakening, unfurling
This heart's fervent longing
Eyes bubbling with dreams
Echoes of a world unseen
Beyond the realm of fantasy
Visions have become reality
What's your name?
- What?
- What's your name?
Richa, come on. Hurry up.
Welcome!
- Not your left hand.
- Sorry.
Enter with your right foot forward.
In the soft hum of a morning anew
Whispers of hope, like gentle dew
Congratulations!
Let's journey together
Forever
In this joyous radiant light
Serve the tea there.
Let's journey together
Forever
Processor...
Sorry, it was an emergency case.
Were you bored?
You'll stain your clothes!
What?
Flower petals leave stains.
Two parts lemon juice,
one part baking soda.
The kitchen is the solution
to every problem.
These headphones are
from my friends.
Do you want them?
Show me.
You keep them.
What else did we get?
A hot-case,
another hot-case,
and a food processor.
Looks like all the gifts
are for you.
How do you like your new house?
It's nice.
Your new family?
They're nice too.
And your new husband?
That's my side of the bed.
The AC stays at 21 degrees.
Is that OK?
Yes.
Shall I turn off the lights?
- Good morning, mummy.
- Good morning, dear.
Should I grind the onions
in the food processor?
Let one wedding gift
be put to some use!
Let it be.
Your father-in-law
wants his chutney stone-ground.
He says a mixer doesn't produce
the same enzymes.
Enzymes?
Yes.
A grindstone crushes,
whereas a mixer just chops.
The flavour isn't the same.
Aunty, veggies for today.
Yes. Take it from her.
Rinse them well
in salt water, OK?
All the pesticides will be washed off.
OK.
It's the bride's first day
in the kitchen.
She will cook halwa!
Of course she will.
The semolina is kept there.
OK.
Mummy, where's the cardamon?
Right there, above.
You're so pretty!
Not as much as you!
My name's Richa.
What's yours?
Saavi.
I have to go to school now.
or else I would help you.
So sweet! I'll manage.
Can you make halwa,
or shall I teach you?
I'll look up the recipe online.
- Which class are you in?
- Third. And you?
In the kitchen 'masterclass'!
Mummy's right here!
One second.
How's the tea?
Nice.
"Almond tea".
- What is it?
- What?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not a pro at all this.
Really?
Your biodata said
you're an expert baker and all!
OK then.
I'll go get dressed.
See you later, wifey!
You're still in the kitchen?
We could've at least
gotten sweets from the market!
You want us to serve outside food
for your daughter's homecoming?
Anyway, Diwakar doesn't like
food from outside.
I'm not fond of it either!
Here you go.
Just one day off a week,
and so many lunch and dinner invites.
Take a proper leave then.
Go for a vacation.
I can't, uncle.
There's too much work.
He's very passionate
about his work, Papa.
Well, so is our Richa!
Really? About what?
Dancing!
Have some more.
Aunty, did you train her
to make all these dishes?
I did try my best!
Those who love good food
can learn how to cook well too.
No worries.
What this mummy couldn't teach her,
her other mummy will. Right?
Of course!
Mummy!
No more, please!
She won't be able to eat all that.
- We'll share from my plate.
- No way.
Madam has cooked everything
after coming back from office.
You must finish everything, OK?
Eat, then.
By the way,
Vishesh mentioned that
you make amazing halwa?
- We won't leave without tasting some!
- For sure.
Let the dishes be, mummy.
The maid will wash them
in the morning.
- The kitchen shouldn't be left dirty.
- Let me help you, then.
Let it be for today.
How was lunch and dinner?
I'm so stuffed, even the mention
of food is making me nauseous.
Shall I wash the cooker?
No, I'll wash it.
I do it everyday.
You go and get some rest.
- Good night.
It's honeymoon time!
Not today. Tomorrow?
What if I'm not
in the mood tomorrow?
Day after tomorrow?
We'll do it again
day after tomorrow!
I've really overeaten today.
Sex is a great antacid!
The medicine box is in the kitchen.
What? Go, get it!
I thought you'd get it for me,
Mr Doctor!
Mummy...
Where's the medicine box?
- Good morning, mummy.
- Good morning.
Wow, fresh butter!
I love fresh butter.
You can chop those vegetables.
Is this size OK?
Make it smaller.
The curry's flavour depends
on how you cut the vegetable.
Let it be, mummy.
The maid can clean it
when she comes.
I can't leave the kitchen
to the maid.
Noticed how often
she's on leave?
Richa?
Yes?
Go, quick.
Check what he wants.
I'll finish cooking and come.
Meftal-Spas?
Yes, you can take it.
Just don't lie down too much.
Your Endometriosis has increased.
Richu, all my clothes.
Shall I dress you up too?
Be my guest.
The clinic has an ultrasound machine.
So, why a new one?
Technology has advanced, Papa.
We need a 4D machine.
Nowadays, senior doctors hire
2-3 doctors under them
and just manage the clinic.
Single practice isn't lucrative anymore.
Patients visit the clinic
for your medical expertise,
and you want to be a manager!
Did you study MBBS or MBA?
One must move with the times.
My father too used to
shun technology before.
Now he uses email
for every little thing.
Serve Papa first.
Not with your left hand.
We don't even give a beggar alms
with the left hand!
Sorry.
Mummy, why don't you sit?
I'll cook the rest and get it.
We can all sit and eat together.
It's not like she has to
go to the clinic and work!
I just thought it would be nice
for us to have breakfast together.
Get Diwakar a hot roti.
Once I'm at the clinic,
I barely get time to drink water.
Get the roti before it burns.
Tea.
I'll get going, wifey.
There are patients waiting.
Madam, shall I clean the house?
Oh, you finally turned up to work!
My wife was sick.
Your wife falls sick
every fifteen days.
Either change your job,
or your wife.
Don't say that, madam.
I'll clean up right away.
And you've stopped dusting
altogether now!
Bubbles! Do a different step here.
What should I do?
And when will you come?
Join us for rehearsals sometime!
How?
Travelling alone takes three hours.
Your dance troupe misses you!
Just come meet us.
Yeah, OK.
I'll figure it out.
Your daughter needs rest,
mummy.
No matter how much I help,
she can only relax
once you're here.
Mummy, I want to talk to you
about something.
Mix this properly, will you?
Spend a few months with us,
please!
You'll get some rest too.
How can I just
leave everything here and come?
Richa can manage the house.
Right?
Yes, of course.
I'm learning how to make
Galouti Kebabs today.
Why don't you visit her?
I'm sure she craves
her mother's cooking.
Thank you for saying that.
I'll book the tickets then, Mom.
I'll send you a list of things
I want from there.
The longer you soak the pumpkin,
the softer the petha will be.
Press it gently from the side.
Quickly. We have lots to make.
It's delicious!
Add a little mustard oil
once it's fully cooked.
- How much?
- A tablespoon or two.
Here, give it to Papa.
Papa, laddoos for you.
You'll manage everything here?
Shall we leave, Ma?
We're getting late.
- Take this. Keep it in your wallet.
- OK.
Let's go.
Good morning, Papa.
Here's your tea.
I haven't cleared my stomach yet.
Your mother-in-law gives me
carom seed water every morning.
Papa, your water.
I cooked the vegetable
with jaggery and tamarind today.
Sweet food early in the morning?
Great.
- Are there no phulkas?
- There are.
Not rotis, I want phulkas.
Hot off the stove.
One minute.
- My dear?
- Yes?
- Is there some curd?
- Yes.
Get me some, please.
Richu, hurry up!
- Papa's waiting.
- Yes!
- My dear...
- Yes?
This chutney isn't stone-ground,
is it?
No Papa, I made it in a mixer.
Grinding chutney with the stone
makes the hands burn, I know.
Never mind.
How much can you manage alone,
after all.
Your mother-in-law is used to it.
Your husband is off to work, wifey!
Give me a nice goodbye
with a smile now.
I smell like shit.
You smell like the kitchen...
And it's the sexiest smell
in the world.
Bye.
Mutton for lunch.
Saheb has sent it.
I'm a dazzling beauty
All eyes are on me
Hold on to your heart
Lest it slips free
I'm a dazzling beauty
Richa?
Hold on to your heart
Lest it slips free
Richa?
Of what use is beauty
Bereft of loyalty
Be a bit attentive, dear.
I've been calling you for a while.
Yes, Papa.
Do you need anything?
No. I'll take it myself.
Set up my lunch.
Sir, lunch wasn't ready.
Shall I get order something?
No, let it be.
Get me a black coffee.
The new bride is taking time
to settle in, isn't it?
- Get me some water.
- Yes, Sir.
Sorry, Papa.
The meat took forever to cook.
Even after four whistles.
You made this in the cooker?
Yes.
Then it's pulao, not biryani.
Dum Pukht Biryani
is cooked on a low flame.
Nice and slow.
Yes.
With patience.
- Yes.
- Layer by layer.
Want some raita?
Thank you.
I work twelve hours everyday.
I deserve lunch on time,
at least.
I barely get time to eat
between patients.
I survived on six black coffees today.
Can I get dinner now?
And hot phulkas, please.
Meena, didn't you teach your assistant
how to cook biryani in a pot?
Make do with pulao
for a few weeks, please.
We'll manage for now, sure...
But Richa must be taught
how to run a house.
At least tell her
to dust the house properly.
If my allergies escalate,
I'll end up getting admitted
in our own hospital!
Hi, hello, namaste,
Sat Sri Akal!
Welcome back to your favourite channel,
King Kalra's Kitchen!
Today's special recipe is
Dum Pukht biryani.
Making Dum Pukht biryani
is an art,
which requires both
technique and love.
So first of all, to make
a delicious, flavourful biryani:
Marinate the chicken
in ginger-garlic paste,
curd and chutney.
That's right!
Now mix these three well.
Boiling rice the right way
is very important.
Remember not to overcook the rice.
Every grain of rice should be distinct.
Onions are another
important ingredient.
They must be finely sliced.
Just like that.
Cook the chicken on low flame.
Let it simmer gradually.
Then in the pot,
add one layer of chicken
and then a layer of rice.
Then another layer of chicken
and another one of rice...
Now seal the pot tight.
You can relax now.
Dum Pukht biryani
will be ready in a bit.
And don't forget
the most important ingredient:
A dollop of your love!
How is it, Papa?
Is there raita?
Yes.
It needs more salt.
There's lots of leftover biryani
from lunch.
Let's have something light
for dinner, please.
But there's so much biryani left.
I made it with so much love.
Which is why I overate...
Can we have kadhi-phulka?
I have no help, Mom.
Diwakar is tired by the time
he's back from work,
and the work in this house
is never-ending.
You have to learn
to handle it, Richu.
I'm trying.
Papa doesn't even
like anything I cook.
Shall I ask them
to hire a cook?
Hush!
You just got married.
Adjust for a while.
After some time,
suggest it tactfully.
I end up eating leftovers
or throwing a ton of food.
Can't you get the portions right?
The portions are right, mom.
It's pointless talking to you.
OK, bye.
- Yeah, Richu.
- Mom...
does the turmeric go
in the curd or in the pan?
No, I'm done. Thanks.
Water?
Done!
Thank you.
My mom doesn't wear a bindi.
She says bindis are only
for women with good luck.
Why is that?
Everyone has good luck.
You don't know anything.
Women without husbands
have no luck.
You're in Class 3, right?
Do you know what
a prime number is?
A number that is unbreakable,
except by itself.
Five, seven...
Eleven, thirteen.
That's what your mom is.
She's a solid Prime Number.
So my mom has good luck?
No.
Because she herself
is a good luck charm!
Now hurry.
Go, win and come back. OK?
Come on, now.
You'll get late.
Diwakar!
Hi.
Look who finally answered!
I thought you never will.
I don't want to talk to you.
Then why did you call?
Because I have great news.
Spill the beans, then!
My performance
has been selected in Kamaani.
My first choreography credit!
Wow!
That's great news!
When do rehearsals begin?
We've already started.
I was calling you since two weeks.
You just didn't answer!
So we went ahead
and started rehearsals.
We have to rehearse daily.
Yes...
It would be very tough
for me to join you guys.
I thought as much.
But come watch
our performance at least.
Hey, please convince her!
Hi, Richa. How are you?
Do come with your husband.
I don't want to get bored alone!
Diwakar doesn't get any time off
from the nursing home.
Madam, it's a Sunday!
No excuses.
You put so much sugar
in the tea!
How will I lose weight?
Richa, her diet plan
changes every week.
You tell me what to do!
So it's a promise, right?
Richu, you don't answer calls,
you don't come for rehearsals,
you're even off social media...
You're OK, right?
I'm fine.
OK, come home for dinner
after the performance.
Like the good ol' days?
- OK. OK, bye.
- Bye!
Papa, the performance
I choreographed in school...
Do you have a video of it?
My dear...
I'll call you back, Papa.
Yes?
The washing machine
doesn't remove sweat stains.
Two parts lemon juice,
one part baking soda.
Kitchen is the solution
to every problem.
- Yes, my dear.
- I'll wash it.
Be gentle. It's my favourite kurta.
Yes, I'll take care.
Diwakar. I texted you.
You didn't call the plumber...
A medical rep gave me
this tablet.
You take it.
I already have one.
The plumber hasn't come yet.
And can we hire a maid
to help with the household work?
Why?
Ved Prakash comes
to mop and clean, right?
Yes, but I want to
start my own work.
I can't find any time for that now.
What work?
You know I'm part of a dance troupe.
Bubbles just got her own show
in Kamaani.
Does this job even pay?
Or is it just for kicks?
It will pay if I work on it.
Richu, I've seen 50-60 patients
through the day...
And you're piling up on me
as soon as I've come home.
Will you let me catch a breath?
Wifey, are you done?
I have to wash the utensils.
Where were you all night, Richu?
I got my period.
What?
I mean, since when?
Just now.
I thought we were
doing everything right...
for you to get pregnant.
Why are you staring at me?
I'm kidding.
Did you go to the kitchen?
- No, I'm going now.
- No need!
Don't enter the kitchen
for 4-5 days.
Why?
Because you need rest.
You relax.
I'll figure out breakfast.
I'll be back.
I need sanitary pads.
The nurse will get them for you.
Please relax!
I'll do the dusting.
Papa has a dust allergy.
Don't worry.
I'll make everything spick and span.
Women in this house
barely get rest, anyway.
Take a break for five days.
Are you a nurse at the clinic?
No, I'm a sweeper there.
But I can do first-aid.
Can you find a maid
to help at the house?
I got so many of them.
They all quit.
People in this house
crib a lot.
I hate to say it, but...
nitpicking, caste-discrimination...
It's rampant here.
I'm from a different caste, you see.
I don't believe in all this.
Or even in period-impurity.
And you shouldn't, either!
Besides, a woman like me
can't afford five days off!
I don't tell anyone
when I'm on my period.
Not that anyone asks me!
You really are a prime number.
What?
Your daughter is lovely.
She adores you!
"I want to grow up
to be like Richa Didi..."
"Richa Didi this,
Richa Didi that..."
She sings your praises
all day!
Who will do the cooking?
Me! Who else?
Your father-in-law says:
"The kitchen fire is very potent."
"It cleanses all impurities!"
Planks are creaking
The boat's leaking
How do we sail through, friend?
No one to hear you whine
As you wine and dine
Are you OK, dear men?
Silent are the sage
While empty vessels rage
Thus goes the old adage
Splutter and jolt, rocks the boat
- How many days has it been?
- Four, sir.
This worn out tale
fed to us since yore
Didn't realise it was a sham
King and queen,
happily ever after
Everyone fell for this scam
Splutter and jolt
Rocks the boat
Splutter and jolt, rocks the boat
I'll do open surgery.
It's the best option
for malignant cases.
What you need
is a good anaesthetist.
Speak to Dr. Pathak.
His son just joined the clinic.
Speak to the senior Dr. Pathak,
trust me.
How is it?
The dal-peetha I made.
Did you like it?
Takes real talent to
botch Mom's special recipe.
I'm just kidding!
It's fine.
I want to discuss something
with both of you.
Sure, tell us.
I'm thinking of applying for a job.
Job?
Why do you need a job?
Papa's right.
One workaholic is enough
for this house, anyway.
Right, Papa?
What's the job?
- Teaching.
- Teaching?
But what will you teach?
I'll be a dance teacher.
It's a part-time job
at a school nearby.
Dance teacher?
I've danced since I was a kid.
I've been teaching since four years.
And I have my own dance troupe, too.
But it's just a hobby, right?
Who turns a hobby into a job?
Yes, and it won't suit
our family's reputation.
The dal-peetha was OK.
Listen...
Don't apply now.
I'll speak to Dad if you want.
Besides, you'll have to quit
after pregnancy anyway.
Right?
Smile.
Richu, look who's here!
We have guests!
Yes?
I got you organic mangoes,
straight from the farm!
Don't they look amazing!
How did you remember
to visit us today?
I had a meeting in Delhi,
so I thought, why not
spend the night here!
Just one night?
Come on, we're family!
No time, man!
You know how it is.
I got fresh sweets!
Try some.
Look who's here!
I'm sure you don't
recognise me.
I bet she doesn't.
Tell me who I am?
Diwakar's cousin, Tunnu bhaiyya
and your wife Binni bhabhi.
Superb!
That's our son, Guddu.
Guddu, say hello to everyone.
How about a cup of strong tea
for everyone?
I'll have a lemon shikanji.
- It's too hot outside for tea.
- Can't you have tea?
How many things will she make?
Don't worry.
She can do it in a jiffy.
What will you have, Guddu?
Cold coffee!
No cold coffee for you.
Have a lemon shikanji!
Richa?
A hot coffee for me.
This calls for a party!
Right?
To Tunnu bhaiyya,
and his terrific idea.
As always!
It's sundown now.
We're past the time for this, right?
Now that she's made it,
why don't you have it?
We're having whiskey now!
OK, fine.
Since you put in so much effort,
I'll have a taste of it.
No thanks.
Making shikanji is an art.
Shikanji can't be made
like lemonade.
Right?
The water must be
chilled just right.
The sugar must be perfect.
A pinch of black salt,
a pinch of cumin,
and a hint of black pepper.
That's a real shikanji.
But, good attempt!
This is a house,
not a restaurant!
A wife who earns
always has an attitude!
OK tell me,
what would you like for dinner?
- Dinner is already made.
- Ved Prakash is getting mutton.
Then I'll cook mutton curry tonight,
followed by my special shikanji!
The proper one.
What say?
No, no!
Please let it be.
We'll cook dinner.
Chill out, Binny!
You ladies relax,
the men shall cook tonight!
OK?
Richa, I need 7-8 onions,
finely chopped.
A bit of ginger-garlic paste,
5-6 tomatoes, chopped...
Do you know how
to marinate mutton?
Binny, marinate it,
will you?
And call us in 30 minutes.
Both brothers
shall cook tonight!
It's decided. Cheers!
Oh God!
This is exactly
what I feared.
Can I help you?
No, I'll manage.
You have to be up early
tomorrow, anyway.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
You won't be used to
this kitchen, anyway.
Mummy! Mummy!
I'm coming!
Richu!
Three shikanjis, quick!
Richu?
I'm getting it!
Richa, dear?
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, Papa.
I'm going for a job interview.
Didn't I advise you
against pursuing a job?
Remember?
You know, your mother-in-law...
She has a PhD,
in Economics.
But her home and kids
were always her first priority.
Now look - Diwakar is a doctor,
and Divya is well settled.
It's a part-time job, Papa.
I've already made
lunch and breakfast
and done the cleaning too.
I'll manage both
the job and house.
We don't have kids yet-
That's the problem
with your generation.
You underestimate
the biological clock.
"Richa Kumar,
care of Dr Ashwin Kumar."
That's the address you wrote
in your application, right?
So then...
You're under my care,
isn't it?
Papa...
You know, she's the reason
I learnt how to dance!
I pushed her
to join the troupe!
I'm doing solo choreography now,
all thanks to her.
And now, she herself has
disappeared from the scene!
When will you come back?
We miss you so much!
Yes, you should go.
You can visit them
once a week, at least.
Really?
Do you go to the clinic
once a week?
I wish!
But that's my job.
- And dancing is their job.
- Exactly.
Not just that -
it's their divine calling.
Hey, relax.
Finish your wine.
I'll clear this up.
Wow!
You're being so helpful here!
So?
Don't I help you at home?
Help?
Forget helping in the kitchen,
he doesn't even budge!
He comes to eat
with his father
and follows him out
when he's done!
'Richu, hot phulkas!'
'Richu, shirt!'
'Richu, tea!'
I too work alone
in the clinic.
Do you help me there?
Really?
As if you'd let me
go out and work?
You found a cook and housemaid
to work for free, after all!
Guys, cassata?
Especially for Richa.
Yes, please.
One big piece for me.
It's her favourite.
Are you drunk?
What are you even saying?
I married you to get
a free cook and maid?
I was kidding, Diwakar.
Is this why
you got me here?
To insult me in front of
your friend and her husband?
Diwakar, please.
I'm a respectable doctor.
Is that how
you'll talk about me?
Please, can we talk later?
- Guys?
- Yes?
Don't bother with the dishes.
I'll load them in the dishwasher later.
Yeah, OK.
It's a huge piece.
I won't be able to finish it.
Why don't you both share it?
Love grows stronger
if you share a plate.
Diwakar?
No, I'm full.
She can finish it.
Of course, she can eat
a whole box of cassata.
Have it.
For you, Babe.
Diwakar?
A couple shouldn't go to bed
angry like this.
Fight with me if you want,
scold me, but talk to me.
Do I really treat you like
an unpaid housemaid?
Can't we move on?
No one even heard it.
I did.
Do you think you made a mistake?
Then maybe, a sorry?
Sorry.
How was the ice cream?
OK-OK.
Just OK?
You gobbled the whole thing,
didn't even offer me a bite!
Richa...
Diwakar?
Ved Prakash told me that
the leakage problem is an old one.
We'll have to change the entire pipeline.
Please get someone to fix this.
Please pack my bag,
I'm leaving for a conference.
It's Papa's birthday
as soon as I'm back.
His friends will be over for lunch.
The food has to be kickass, OK?
I'll work on the menu.
The packing is done.
Need anything else?
Yes.
I need something else
from you.
The taxi won't be here
for another twenty minutes...
Diwakar, please.
Let's not waste
your ovulation period.
Diwakar, please!
What happened?
Is everything alright?
What's wrong with you, Richa?
What's the problem?
I'm talking to you!
What's going on?
Is sex only to make babies?
We're married...
Family planning
is important, right?
Planning? Like this?
By having mechanical sex?
What do you mean?
How do you not realise, Diwakar?
I feel pain! Can't you see?
So even sex with me
is painful now?
Yes!
Sex shouldn't be a task.
Like you finish,
and it's 'task over'!
Where's the intimacy, Diwakar?
What about foreplay?
I too have desires!
You just get on top
and start off!
And the moment you're done...
So...
You're pretty experienced!
Sex expert, eh?
Desires...
You think you're worth desiring?
You stink of the kitchen!
Have you looked into
the mirror lately?
"Mechanical sex!"
Richa?
I'm here to substitute
for your mother-in-law today!
I got you the Karwa Chauth
morning meal.
Namaste, Aunty.
Have you decided what
you'll wear tomorrow?
Have a heavy meal tonight.
Tomorrow, you can't
even drink water.
- Guddu...
- Yes?
You used to make
fantastic sabudana khichdi, right?
- Yes!
- Please do make it tomorrow.
Sure, I will.
I've also brought guavas for you.
- I'll make a curry out of them.
- Superb.
Richa, do me a favour.
Chop the guavas for now.
I'll go get mango powder.
Why don't you just rest for a bit?
I'll take care of this.
I've come here to help you!
I'm on mom-in-law duty,
remember?
Richa?
The cleaner the kitchen,
the more prosperous the home.
Yes, Aunty.
The entire pipeline
needs to be changed.
Eeks!
The bottle's all greasy.
- Aunty!
- Yes?
Here's the chicken
for tonight's dinner.
And peas for tomorrow
and the day after.
Richa...
This is my chicken recipe.
I love cooking.
I taught your mother-in-law
to cook, too.
I love dancing.
Dance?
What dance?
I'm a dancer.
I have a dance troupe, too.
Let me show you.
Look.
That must be Diwakar.
Diwakar!
Look at you.
People gain weight after marriage,
and you're just getting thinner!
What can I do, Aunty -
she hogs all the food!
Please take your meds on time
during the Karwa Chauth fast.
Skipping medicines one day
won't kill me!
- Fasting is good for health.
- Yes.
All our traditions like Karwa Chauth
are well thought out.
Every tradition is backed
with scientific reasoning.
You're absolutely right.
- Some tomato-jaggery chutney?
- Yes, please.
- Why don't you train her?
- She'll learn eventually.
- Are you OK?
- Yes.
- It's just my BP and diabetes.
- I'll get your medicines.
No way! No medicines.
I'm fasting!
Fasting shouldn't be compulsory.
Take your medicine.
I have no difficulty fasting!
I've been doing it for years.
Your generation has
no will power!
Focus on your own fast.
Your mother-in-law told me
you nibble at food while cooking?
I hope you won't
polish off all the paneer
and just serve us
plain gravy!
Now go keep the medicine back.
Look! Do I look like a prime number?
Of course.
You're a prime number, too!
You think so?
Yes!
- Do you remember the prime numbers?
- Yes.
One, three, five,
seven, eleven...
Numbers that are unbreakable
except by themselves.
Richa!
What's this?
They're old videos, Diwakar.
You know about them.
I thought these were private.
I'm not well-versed
with social media.
This doesn't look good.
Delete them.
I won't.
If you want to live in this house,
you have to follow its rules.
Delete them, or-
Or what?
What will you do?
Touch his feet.
Give her a sip of water.
Congratulations!
Your first Karwa Chauth!
Let's go sit.
Diwakar!
Aunty, at least stay
for the party?
No. My work here is done.
I have my own household to run!
Ved!
Get more balloons.
Mr Mehta, please come!
Oh, you shouldn't have...
- Thank you, thank you so much.
- Many happy returns of the day!
Mr Agarwal, how are you?
You didn't have to...
Thank you so much.
So nice of you to come!
Thank you.
Beautiful flowers!
Thank you so much.
Take this.
Where's the photographer?
Where is he?
Ved Prakash?
Where's the photographer?
Take a picture.
Happy Birthday to you!
You're 65, old man!
If we all stand united,
our country will be unbeatable!
Absolutely.
If that's the case,
why are you moving abroad?
Good question.
It's too hot here.
That reminds me...
Shikanji? Shikanji?
With gin?
Not just gin,
It goes with vodka, green chillies
- Sweet, salted, you name it!
- But Tunnu Bhaiyya...
Let's do a show of hands.
Anybody for shikanji?
- One, two, three, four...
- One for me, too!
Everyone's thirsty now!
Bhabhi, they've asked for
nine glasses of lemonade.
Two sweet and salted,
three sweet,
two salted, four without ice,
and one with green chillies.
Diwakar, check out this step!
What are you doing,
Tunnu Bhaiyya?
Aren't you on social media?
They're your wife's
dance moves!
Come on!
Didn't I ask you
to delete those videos?
You've humiliated me
in front of everyone!
And where the hell
is the shikanji!
Everyone's been waiting!
Have you gone crazy, Richa?
You need a tight slap!
Sweetie, that's your home now.
Who walks out of their home
over such a small issue?
I'll come along with you.
Just say sorry.
Sis, when did you come?
It's so hot outside.
Calm down, Richu.
Go, have a glass of cold water.
And get one for your brother, too.
- Go.
- I won't.
Why should I?
Can't he get it himself?
It's parents like you
who spoil their sons rotten!
What's the big deal, sweetie?
Don't patronise me!
I'm your daughter!
Sweetie this, sweetie that!
Daughters deserve the same
love and respect as sons!
Sorry, the first phulka
got a bit burnt...
It's alright.
First attempts often go wrong.
Second time's the charm!
I've left it all behind
Bindi.
This journey is mine
- Are you all ready?
- Yes.
Warm up a bit.
Today I step into
a world of my own
Wow, who got you the bouquet?
I got it. For myself.
It was lost
Left unknown
A name of my own
We will rise like a phoenix
Each time we fall
We will bloom into the spring
We will give it our all
Why not be your own soulmate?
No one but you can own your fate
Learn to trust your heart
We'll rise like a phoenix
Each time we fall
We'll bloom into the spring
We'll give it our all
Obscuring your vision
When darkness creeps in
Illuminate your path
With the light within
You're a flame set ablaze
You're the roar that resonates
Far across every land
We'll rise like a phoenix
Each time we fall
We'll bloom into the spring
We'll give it our all
For ages you held a fire
Brewing within you
Now it shows the path
As you break out
of your shadow
Its sparks flickering
Like the moon rising
Look, behold
A thing of such beauty
We will rise like a phoenix
Each time we fall
We will bloom into the spring
We will give it our all